var french = [
	{
		front: "the boy",
		back: "le garcon"
	}, {
		front: "the girl",
		back: "la fille"
	}, {
		front: "the man",
		back: "l'homme"
	},{
		front: "the woman",
		back: "la femme"
	}, {
		front: "the family",
		back: "la famille"
	}, {
		front: "the house",
		back: "la maison"
	}, {
		front: "the food",
		back: "la nourriture"
	}, {
		front: "hello",
		back: "bonjour"
	}, {
		front: "good morning",
		back: "bonjour"
	}, {
		front: "good evening",
		back: "bonsoir"
	}, {
		front: "goodbye",
		back: "au revoir"
	}, {
		front: "please",
		back: "s'il vous plait"
	}, {
		front: "thank you",
		back: "merci"
	}
];

module.exports = french;